Hello everyone
مرحبا جميعا
welcome back to our English listening practice.
مرحبا بعودتنا إلى ممارسة الاستماع إلى اللغة الإنجليزية.
How are you today?
كيف حالك اليوم؟
Is your listening getting better now?
هل أصبح استماعك أفضل الآن؟
Did you turn off the subtitles and try
هل أوقفت الترجمة وحاولت
to listen carefully?
أن تستمع جيدا؟
I hope so.
آمل ذلك.
Today's story is not only about me,
قصة اليوم ليست عني فقط،
it's also about my friends, Mike and Jasmine
كما أنه يتعلق بأصدقائي، مايك وياسمين
Do you remember Mike and Jasmine?
هل تتذكر مايك وياسمين؟
We met at college.
التقينا في الجامعة.
They became some of our friends.
أصبحوا من أصدقائنا.
If you haven't watched my college story yet,
إذا لم تشاهد قصتي عن الجامعة بعد،
make sure to watch it.
تأكد من مشاهدته.
I will leave you the link in the description box.
سأترك لك الرابط في مربع الوصف.
After you finish this lesson, write in the comments
بعد أن تنهي هذا الدرس، اكتب في التعليقات
how do you feel after practicing with us?
كيف تشعر بعد التدريب معنا؟
Today, we will talk about a fun topic,
اليوم، سنتحدث عن موضوع ممتع،
going to the beach.
ذاهبون إلى الشاطئ.
Let me ask you, have you ever visited
دعني أسألك، هل سبق لك أن زرت؟
a beach in another country?
شاطئ في بلد آخر؟
Do you want to ask for something
هل تريد أن تطلب شيئا
but don't know how to say it in English?
لكن لا تعرف كيف تقولها بالإنجليزية؟
Maybe you wanted to rent a sunbed or
ربما أردت استئجار سرير تشمس أو
order a drink, but you weren't sure what
اطلب مشروبا، لكنك لم تكن متأكدا مما هو
words to use.
كلمات لاستخدامها.
Today, I want you to think what situations
اليوم، أريدك أن تفكر في المواقف
at the beach might make you feel confused
على الشاطئ قد يجعلك تشعر بالارتباك
or nervous.
أو متوترا.
Don't worry, I will speak slowly and clearly
لا تقلق، سأتحدث ببطء ووضوح
so you can follow easily.
لذا يمكنك المتابعة بسهولة.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟